Hello

I'm Brandon Heinrich

1331 Green Bay St La Crosse, WI 54601 1-608-852-3005 BrandonRayHeinrich@Gmail.com

Objective

My goal is to get a job doing what I love. Since I was 10 years old I've always loved programming. I want to work in a field that will challenge me every day, and give me many chances at personal growth.

I am have shown my proficiency in C++, Java, C, and C# in both the workplace and university setting. In addition to that, I have a passion for Python, Prolog, and Lisp-like languages. I am very good at picking up new skills, and take a great deal of pride in my work.

Experience

January 2016 - PRESENT

Trane, La Crosse, WI - Software Engineer Intern

- Fixed bugs in legacy software using C++
- Helped with the onboarding of a second intern
- Created reports using DevExpress and .NET 4.6 in C#
- Debugged issues with our remote team in India

November 2010 - October 2015

Pizza Hut, Cottage Grove & La Crosse, WI -

- Assisted in the training of new employees
- Prepared food, attended to customers, cleaned, and performed routine maintenance

Education

September 2013 - December 2016

University of Wisconsin, La Crosse - Computer Science, Mathematics Double Major

GPA of 2.87 and Dean's List for 2 semesters

Relevant Coursework: Differential Geometry, Galois Theory, Structure of Compilers, Programming Language Concepts, Simulation.

Awards

Placed 27th out of over 300 in Association for Computing Machinery's International Collegiate Programming Contest North Central America regional competition in 2013